{
    "id": "8423da40d19f4affb39d8a0a5b406a32",
    "title": "Approve, Oppose, Object | Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They ............................ to the manager's decisions.",
            "description": "'Objected' takes the preposition 'to' before an object. 'Oppose' does not take a preposition before an object. ",
            "answers": [
                "objected",
                "opposed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f352805acf7a4b4ebd6e43024c06ff77"
        },
        {
            "question": "The family ............................ her new fiance.",
            "description": "Approve takes the preposition 'of' before an object. ",
            "answers": [
                "approves",
                "approves of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af456b8452644edc9a28898c984ae585"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are ............................. the idea.",
            "description": "Object takes the preposition 'to' before the object.",
            "answers": [
                "objected",
                "objected to",
                "opposed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c3537af1d5c240a1aa0586e7b87fcbed"
        },
        {
            "question": "In this state, parental ........................... is necessary before a seventeen-year old can obtain a driver's license.",
            "description": "Approval is the noun form.",
            "answers": [
                "approve",
                "approval",
                "approving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f326b5aa3687425db678890e1e5b98b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I object ........................... this.",
            "description": "Here the 'to' after 'object' is a preposition. When 'to' is used as a preposition, it is followed by an -ing form, not an infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "to do",
                "doing",
                "to doing"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "4fc1d2c1d6cf4d638e7ffeab003d45f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mother ........................... cigar smoking.",
            "description": "The verb 'object' needs the preposition 'to' before an object. ",
            "answers": [
                "objects",
                "objects to",
                "object to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "71fd3fc9d6d94c10a2b8742486047e64"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy kept the dog despite his sister's ........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "object",
                "objective",
                "objection"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "771c7823eea24b888fb75f485e145fb8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is rude and ...........................",
            "description": "Objectionable means intolerable. ",
            "answers": [
                "objective",
                "objectionable",
                "object"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0cf8592618094aa1b95e61775236efc6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Several of the speakers .......................... the project.",
            "description": "'Objected' takes the preposition 'to' before an object. 'Oppose' does not take a preposition before an object. ",
            "answers": [
                "opposed",
                "objected",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e02ac1d2a7a401dbeb2611003c9d62c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many people are ............................. to the idea.",
            "description": "Oppose can have both passive and active uses. Object is not used like this. ",
            "answers": [
                "objected",
                "opposed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd38a4ed666649d18f8fea21fa46266a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The senate ............................. the new housing bill.",
            "description": "When approve means 'pass' it does not take a preposition before the object. ",
            "answers": [
                "approved",
                "approved of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "339b23757bec4d289a1877c4a1914031"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child did something his father did not .....................",
            "description": "'Approve of' means judge as good or think highly of.",
            "answers": [
                "approve",
                "approve of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "71175c3e873b420c84a9c3945bde90e8"
        }
    ]
}